http://www.cpilink.com/privacy-policy

Catalytic Oxidizers
Regenerative Thermal Oxidizer (RTO)
Catalyst
Catalyst Services (Testing, Cleaning, Rejuvenation)
Catalytic Oxidizers
Regenerative Thermal Oxidizer (RTO)
Catalyst
Catalyst Services (Testing, Cleaning, Rejuvenation)
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyCatalytic Products InternationalPrivacy Policy Effective May 22, 2018
Catalytic Products International (CPI) recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information provided to us. Accordingly, we strive for compliance with all federal and state privacy laws and follow industry best practices in order to best serve our community. The following guidelines have been created to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. It applies to all of our publications, books, events and properties.
CPI has made a commitment to comply with all privacy and data protection requirements imposed by both the US Department of Commerce and the European Union (“EU”). This includes the recent General Data Protection Regulation. To that end, recipients of our electronic communications who have not affirmatively opted in to receive communications will be given an opportunity to do so. Opt-out links will also be provided in all of our electronic communications and on our site to unsubscribe from future communications.
In order to service our customers and facilitate future communications and interaction with customers and prospects, we collect and store information on our site thru the use of “cookies”. We collect and store only the information required for these purposes. For contacts located in the EU, you will be provided an opportunity to opt into our system by accepting the terms and conditions of both our electronic communications process and website use before we use a “cookie” to collect and store information.
We promise to protect all information collected and stored, and upon request we will provide a complete copy of all information stored for the customer or prospective customer. We will also delete all information stored for marketing purposes, including your IP address, upon receipt of any request to delete the information by clicking this link . CPI reserves the right to continue using the deleted stored information for any “lawful basis” , which includes customer collection purposes.
All questions regarding our policy should be directed to info@cpilink.com.
Our location and contact information:
Catalytic Products International 980 Ensell Road Lake Zurich, IL 60047 Phone (847) 438-0334 Fax (847) 438-0944
Collected InformationThe information we collect is gathered from several sources, which include product subscriptions, purchases or registrations, either from print or online forms; reader service cards; website message postings; survey information and direct or indirect purchases via telephone, direct mail, email, and other electronic sources. From these sources we may collect postal addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers, and/or demographic information for those individuals that volunteer such information. For each visitor to our websites, our web server automatically recognizes the visitor’s domain name and IP address only. No other identifiable information is collected unless volunteered. In addition, we collect aggregate information on what web pages visitors visit.
How We Use Collected InformationThe information we collect is used to improve the content of our web pages, to customize the content and layout of our pages for each individual visitor, and/or to notify visitors about updates to our website. As part of a subscription, purchase and/or registration agreement, subscribers, purchasers and registrants will be contacted by us through mail, e-mail, and/or phone to communicate with them about their subscription, purchase and/or registration. They will be contacted for renewal, re-qualification, surveys, updates concerning their account profile and special offers related to their subscription, purchase and/or registration. We also use the information to contact them for marketing purposes on behalf of other reputable organizations, but we never share or give-away this collected information.
Standard E-mail CommunicationsIf you have registered for our products and/or services, and have supplied an e-mail address, you will receive emails pertaining to your subscription, purchase and/or registration. These are sent to maintain your account with Catalytic Products International. You can 'opt-out' from receiving these types of e-mails at any time.
Marketing E-Mail CommunicationsFor marketing e-mails, we retain three types of usage permission for submitted e-mail addresses as defined below. You can 'opt out' of receiving marketing e-mails about Catalytic Products International products and from outside companies either in response to a received e-mail or within this Privacy Policy.
E-mails about Related Products and ServicesIf you volunteer an e-mail address you may be contacted by us regarding other products, services and/or upcoming events that are related to our Strings or Acoustic Guitar Publishing Groups within which your account resides. If you do not wish to receive these types of e-mails from us, please let us know by calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address. You can also 'opt-out' from receiving these types of e-mails by using the opt-out mechanism located within the received e-mail message.
E-mails about Other Catalytic Products International Products and ServicesIf you volunteer an e-mail address you may be contacted by us regarding any other Catalytic Products International products, services, and/or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive these types of e-mails from us, please let us know by calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address. You can also 'opt-out' from receiving these types of e-mails by using the opt-out mechanism located within the received e-mail message.
E-mails from Outside CompaniesIf you volunteer an e-mail address you may be contacted by carefully selected outside companies for reputable promotional purposes. If you do not wish to receive e-mails from other companies, please let us know by calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address. You can also 'opt-out' from receiving these types of e-mails by using the opt-out mechanism located within the received e-mail message.
All E-mailsIf you wish to opt-out of these three types of e-mail marketing messages at once, please let us know by calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address.
It will take up to ten business days to process your e-mail opt-out request. Please note that you may receive additional communications from us or an outside company after submitting your request if your e-mail address was selected from our database just prior to receiving and processing your request.
Postal CommunicationsIf you volunteer a postal address you may receive periodic mailings to relate information about new products, services, and/or upcoming events. We may also provide this information to other carefully selected outside companies for promotional purposes. If you do not wish to receive mailings from us or other companies, please let us know by calling us at [1-847-438-0334], or writing to us at the above address.
It will take up to three months to process your do-not-mail request. Please note that you may receive additional communications from us or other companies after submitting your request if your postal address was selected from our database just prior to receiving and processing your request.
Telephone CommunicationsIf you volunteer a telephone number you may receive periodic telephone calls about new products, services, and/or upcoming events. We may also provide this information to carefully selected outside companies for promotional purposes. If you do not wish to receive telephone calls from us, please let us know by calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address.
It will take up to one month to process your do-not-call request. Please note that you may receive additional communications from us or other companies after submitting your request if your telephone number was selected from our database just prior to receiving and processing your request.
Fax CommunicationsIf you volunteer a fax number you may receive promotional faxes on a very limited basis. Only those with whom we have an existing business relationship (such as an established subscription or registration) will receive such faxes. If you do not wish to receive such faxes, please let us know by calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address.
Accessing Personal Information Upon request, we will provide an individual with access to identifying information that we have collected about them (provided that they have given proof of identity). This information can be requested by writing to us at the above address.
Correcting/Updating Personal InformationUpon request, we offer individuals the ability to have inaccuracies corrected within their contact information. This information can be corrected by writing to us at the above address. Current subscribers and registrants can also access and change their information through our websites by selecting the appropriate link on the website where their current subscription/registration resides.
CookiesOur Site uses “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to be alerted when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. This website uses Google Analytics (GA) to help analyze how users interact with www.cpilink.com. CPI does not collect personal identifiers, just numbers associated with Users devices and demographic data is only available.
By using our website, you agree to the use and processing of your data by Google, as described above with data retention settings set to not expire. You can opt out from being tracked by GA across the internet by downloading and installing Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on at: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
CPI uses Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise trigger across the Internet. AdWords remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the CPI website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. THIS COOKIE DOES NOT IN ANYWAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER The cookie is used to say “This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page.” Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.  Information about how visitors can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's Ads Settings.
Sharing Your Personal Information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Links
This site may contain links to other websites in the form of hyperlinks. Catalytic Products International is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
SecurityCatalytic Products International takes every precaution to protect your information from unauthorized use. When you submit sensitive information via our websites, the information is protected both online and offline. Our site is protected by Verisign and its recognized logo. We will never ask you for credit card or bank-related information through our website..
Changes to Privacy PolicyWe may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not disclosed in this privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, bookmark this page and check back periodically.
CONTACT US
QUICK LINKS
Careers
Contact
FAQS
Home
News
Privacy
Catalytic Products International980 Ensell RoadLake Zurich, IL 60047-1557
Phone:  847.438.0334
Copyright 2020 Catalytic Products International
Quote
Case Studies
